He never met a target he couldn't take. Until today.
Killshot is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by John Madden.
Beautiful Carmen Colson and her ironworker husband Wayne are placed in the
Federal Witness Protection program after witnessing an "incident".
Thinking they are at last safe, they are targeted by an experienced
hit man and a psychopathic young upstart killer.
Armand 'The Blackbird' Degas, played by Mickey Rourke.
Carmen Colson, played by Diane Lane.
Wayne Colson, played by Thomas Jane.
Donna, played by Rosario Dawson.
Richie Nix, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Blackbird's Kid Brother, played by Brandon McGibbon.
Killshot is a 2008 American action thriller independent film directed by John Madden, and
starring Diane Lane, Thomas Jane, Mickey Rourke and Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
It is based on Elmore Leonard's 1989 novel of the same name.
The story follows a couple who, despite being in a Witness Protection Program,
are being chased and confronted by the criminal they outed.
The tone is emotional and intense.